ROSE GRONDIN

Full Stack developer

(514) 659-1419 • rose.grondin@gmail.com • Montreal, QC, Canada in 🖸

PROFILE

Business school graduate, 3 years as an SEO specialist. I just completed a 9-week, full-stack web development bootcamp. Eager and motivated to keep learning, I'm seeking a great team to join for the next chapter of my journey.Loyal, a team player, great multitasker, and a fast learner. I can adapt to any new situation.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon Montreal

Full stack coding bootcamp batch #367 January - March 2020

HEC Montreal

Bachelor in Business Administration
- Marketing

2010 - 2014

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
- APIs, JSON, scraping
- Relational databases, SQL, Postgres
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- ES6 Javascript
- Wireframes, prototyping, UI design
- Test driven development
- Git, Github, technical workflow
- Currently learning React & Redux
- Figma
- Google analytics certification

LANGUAGES

- French (native)
- English (fluent)

EXPERIENCE

AOD marketing - SEO specialist & online visibility

Aug 2017 - Nov 2019

Project Manager - Manage SEO & social media teams as well as the website rebranding project

SEO - Perform technical SEO audits and provide recommendations to clients

Web visibility - Define online visibility strategies & budget according to different customer objectives

AOD marketing - Online relations & social media analyst

Apr 2016 - Aug 2017

Planning & Strategy - Define online visibility strategies & budget according to different customer objectives

Influencer marketing - Define, prospect, contact, negotiate qualify potential influencers for each campaign

Content - Create content or support influencers in content creation

Anugo media - Marketing coordinator

Oct 2015 - Mars 2016

Implementation of the marketing strategy
Other administrative tasks

PERSONAL PROJECTS

<u>Green Thumb</u> - Your garden companion: a new way to manage your home garden

<u>Stellactica</u> - Market place to rent your planets & invade someone else's

<u>Cocktailadvisor</u> - Create your cocktails & rates others cocktails recipes